{
    "subject": "resource/NetSuite",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundingYear",
    "object": "1998",
    "human_readable": "NetSuite was founded in 1998.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8739237785339355,
            "question": "What event happened in the year 1998 related to NetSuite?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8701362013816833,
            "question": "When was NetSuite founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6765772700309753,
            "question": "Was NetSuite founded before or after the turn of the millennium?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6445847749710083,
            "question": "In what decade was NetSuite established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5706546902656555,
            "question": "Does the founding year of NetSuite suggest it's a pioneer in its industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5459163784980774,
            "question": "What year did NetSuite come into existence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4040137231349945,
            "question": "What can we infer about the age of NetSuite based on its founding year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23934108018875122,
            "question": "Is NetSuite a relatively new or old company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13216853141784668,
            "question": "If today is 2023, how many years has NetSuite been operating?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10524288564920425,
            "question": "How old will NetSuite be in the year 2038?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=NetSuite was founded in 1998.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4482_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today is 2023, how many years has NetSuite been operating?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4482_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is NetSuite a relatively new or old company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4482_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we infer about the age of NetSuite based on its founding year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4482_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4482_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`\n\nThe documents provided clearly state that NetSuite was founded in 1998, both in the first document and several other subsequent documents. This information is consistently mentioned throughout the context, making it a verifiable fact based on the given texts."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that NetSuite was indeed founded in 1998."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}